<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Bulk Steel Extraction Revived</name>
    <author>Adda</author>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.1</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <packageId>Adda.BulkSteelExtractionRevived</packageId>
    <url></url>
    <description>
This is a revival of an original mod Bulk Steel Extraction by Fuglypump for RimWorld 1.1, which adds new bills to the Electric Smelter allowing you to extract steel from slag chunks and debris.

I also added modifiable mod settings in Mod Settings section.
––––––––––––
New recipes
Electric Smelter (no research required)
– Extract metal from Slag (x3) – smelt 3 slag chunks at a time for 60 steel (changeable),
– Extract metal from debris – smelt 1 stone chunk for 10 steel (changeable),
– Extract metal from debris (x3) – smelt 3 stone chunks at a time for 30 steel (changeable).

Mod settings
Allows you to change:
– amount of steel to extract steel from a single slag chunk,
– amount of work to extract steel from a single slag chunk,
– amount of steel to extract steel from a single stone chunk,
– amount of work to extract steel from a single stone chunk,
– option to get an extra component from smelting a single slag chunk,
– option to get an extra component from smelting a single stone chunk.

Notes
Recipes which smelt 3 chunks at a time cost 25 % less work than smelting single chunks at a time.
Smelting stone chunks costs by default the same amount of work as smelting chunks of slag. (changeable)

––––––––––––
Compatibility and other mods
Mod is safe to add to your saved games or delete from them. Just make sure you delete all the added bills and/or electric smelter before uninstalling to avoid any possible errors – you would get a few harmless errors (but it might have even a bigger impact with greater severity).

Required mods
None.

Recommended mods
None.

Compatible mods
[1.1] Cupro's Stones by Ogliss and Dr Zhivago – Adds 10 new types of stone and updates the stone graphics for more realism. My mod supports the usage of new stone types for extracting steel from debris.

Mod should be fully compatible with every other mod. Though I expect there might be some issues with other mods so if you find any incompatibility, let me know in the discussion below so I could fix it or at least give you a warning.

Known incompatible mods
SF More Steel from Slag by Rainbeau Flambe and SheiFoxy – This mods adds the same mod settings options as my revival but without an option for adjusting values for smelting debris. Therefore it is unnecessary and this mod and my mod would be overwriting each other's settings.

Steel Extraction by Retrific – Both mods add recipes for smelting stone debris, these will either be overwritten or appear twice. Therefore it is incompatible with my mod.

If you find any incompatibility, let me know in the discussion below so I could fix it or at least give you a warning.

Load order
Just load this anywhere below Core and you should be good to go.

Load order should not be affected by any other mods but if you find any problems, just let me know in the discussion below so I can fix them.

––––––––––––
Credits
Original mod: Bulk Steel Extraction by Funglypump – I have used this mod's code and changed it, added mod settings options and updated for RimWorld 1.1.

SF More Steel from Slag by Rainbeau Flambe and SheiFoxy – The code for mod's settings in RimWorld's Mod Settings was based on this mod's mod settings. I used the code and edited it for usage purposes of this mod.

License
All original code in this mod is licensed under the MIT license. Do whatever you might want to do with my mod, but would be nice if you would give me credit for the original mod/idea :)
    </description>
</ModMetaData>
